### Privacy Policy

**The Mirror Privacy Policy**

**_Last modified: 9/13/2023_**

**Introduction**

This policy applies to your access to and use of the downloadable software, websites, mobile applications and other online products and services (collectively, the “**Services**”) available at [https://in.themirror.space](https://in.themirror.space/) via download and/or through the mobile application version of the Services (collectively, the “**Platform**” or “**The Mirror**”) provided by The Mirror Megaverse Inc. (“**TMM**”, or “**we**”).

This policy applies to information we collect:

* Through our Service;
* In email, text, and other electronic messages between you and this Company;
* Through mobile and desktop applications you download from the internet, which provide dedicated non-browser-based interaction between you and this Service; and
* When you interact with our advertisements and applications on third-party websites and services, if those applications or advertisements include links to this policy.

It does not apply to information collected by:

* Use offline or a different means (including on any other website) operated by the Company or any third party; or
* Any third-party (including our affiliates and subsidiaries), including through any application or content (including advertising) that may link to or be accessible from or on the Service.

Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it.  If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your choice is not to use our Service.  By accessing or using our Service, you agree to this privacy policy.  This policy may change from time to time (_see_ [Changes to Our Privacy Policy](http://%5Cl%20%22SD_ChangesPrivacyPolicy%22)).  Your continued use of this Service after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the policy periodically for updates.

**Children Under the Age of 18**

**Our Service is not intended for children under 18 years of age.  No one under age 18 may provide any information to or on the Service.  We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 18.  If you are under 18, do not use or provide any information on this Service, or on/or through any of its features.  If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under 18 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information.  If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 18, please contact us at:** [\[email protected\]](https://www.themirror.space/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)**. Information We Collect About You and How We Collect It**

We collect several types of information from and about users of our Service, including information:

* By which you may be personally identified; such as name, postal address, e-mail address, telephone number, social security number, and any other identifier by which you may be contacted online or offline (“**Personal Information**”);
* That is about you but individually does not identify you; and/or
* About your internet connection, the equipment you use to access our Service, and usage details.

We collect this information:

* Directly from you when you provide it to us;
* Automatically as you navigate through the service, (Information collected automatically may include usage details, IP addresses, and information collected through cookies.); and
* From third-parties; for example, our business partners and analytics software providers.

**Information You Provide to Us**

The information we collect on/or through our Service may include:

* Information that you provide by filling in forms on our Platform, (This includes information provided at the time of registering to use our Service, subscribing to our Service, posting material, or requesting further services.  We may also ask you for information when you enter a promotion sponsored by us, and when you report a problem with our Platform.);
* Records and copies of your correspondence (including email addresses) if you contact us;
* Your responses to surveys that we might ask you to complete for research purposes.
* Details of agreements you enter into through our Service, and of the fulfillment of your agreements.  You may be required to provide financial information before entering into an agreement through our Service.  To engage in certain transactions, you may need to provide us, or our third-party payment processors, with your payment information and allow us to connect to your bank account by providing us with your banking details.  We will never ask you for your personal access information.  We do not directly collect or store any payment card information entered through our services or access your bank account, but we may receive the information from our third-party payment processing providers, associated with your payment card information.
* Your search queries on the Platform.

**Information We Collect Through Automatic Data Collection Technologies**

As you navigate through and interact with our Service, we may use automatic data collection technologies to collect certain information about your equipment, (browsing actions and patterns), including:

* Details of your interactions with our Service, including traffic data, location data, logs, and other communication data, and the resources that you access and use on the Platform.
* Information about your computer and internet connection, including your IP address, operating system, and browser type.

The information we collect automatically may include personal information, or we may maintain it or associate it with personal information we collect in other ways or receive from third-parties.  It helps us to improve our Platform and to deliver a better and more personalized service, including by enabling us to:

* Estimate our audience size and usage patterns;
* Store information about your preferences, (allowing us to customize our application according to your individual interests);
* Speed up your searches;
* Recognize you for later uses of our Service;

The technologies we use for this automatic data collection may include:

* **Cookies (or browser cookies)**.  A cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer or mobile device.  You may refuse to accept browser cookies, by activating the appropriate setting on your computer.  However, if you select this setting, you may be unable to access certain parts of our Service.  Unless you have adjusted your computer setting, (so that it will refuse cookies), our system will issue cookies when you direct your computer to our Service.
* **Flash Cookies**.  Certain features of our Service may use locally stored objects (or Flash cookies) to collect and store information about your preferences, and navigation to, from, and/on our Platform.  Flash cookies are not managed by the same computer or mobile device settings, as are used for browser cookies.  For information about managing your privacy and security settings for Flash cookies, _see_ [Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information](http://%5Cl%20%22SD_ChoicesAboutUse%22).

**Third-Party Use of Cookies**

* Some content or applications, (including advertisements), on the Service are served by third-parties, (including advertisers, ad networks and servers; content providers and application providers).  These third parties may use cookies to collect information about you when you use our Service.  The information they collect may be associated with your personal information or they may collect information, (including personal information), about your online activities over time, and across different websites and other online services.  They may use this information to provide you with interest-based (behavioral) advertising or other targeted content.
* We do not control these third-parties’ tracking technologies or how they may be used.  If you have any questions about an advertisement or other targeted content, you should contact the responsible provider directly.

**How We Use Your Information**

We use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any personal information:

* To present our Platform and its contents to you;
* To provide you with information, products, or services that you request from us;
* To fulfill any other purpose for which you provide it.
* To provide you with notices about your account, including expiration and renewal notices;
* To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, including for billing and collection;
* To notify you about changes to our Service or any products or services we offer or provide though it;
* To allow you to participate in interactive features on our Platform;
* In any other way we may describe when you provide the information; and
* For any other purpose with your consent.

We may also use your information to contact you about goods and services that may be of interest to you.  If you do not want us to use your information in this way, please adjust your user preferences in your account profile.

We may use the information we have collected from you to enable us to display advertisements to our advertisers’ target audiences.  Even though we do not disclose your personal information for these purposes without your consent, if you click on/or otherwise interact with an advertisement, the advertiser may assume that you meet its target criteria.

**Disclosure of Your Information**

We may disclose aggregated information about our users without restriction.

We may disclose personal information that we collect, or you provide as described in this privacy policy:

* To our subsidiaries and affiliates;
* To contractors, service providers, and other third-parties we use to support our business;
* To a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, or other sale or transfer of some or all of TMM’s assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar proceeding, in which personal information held by TMM about our Users is among the assets transferred;
* To fulfill the purpose for which you provide it;
* For any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information;
* To comply with any court order, law, or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request;
* To enforce or apply our Terms of Use, including for billing and collection purposes; and
* If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of TMM, our Users, or others.  (This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.)

**Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information**

We strive to provide you with choices regarding the personal information you provide to us.  We have created mechanisms to provide you with the following control over your information:

* **Tracking Technologies and Advertising**.  Do Not Track (“**DNT**”) is a privacy preference that users can set in certain web browsers.  You can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent.  If you disable or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of this Service may then be inaccessible, or not function properly.
* **Disclosure of Your Information for Third-Party Advertising**.  If you do not want us to share your personal information with unaffiliated or non-agent third-parties for promotional purposes, you can opt-out by sending us an email stating your request to [\[email protected\]](https://www.themirror.space/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).  
* **Promotional Offers from the Company**.  If you do not wish to have your contact information used by the Company to promote our own or third-parties’ products or services, you can opt-out by sending us an email stating your request to [\[email protected\]](https://www.themirror.space/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).  If we have sent you a promotional email, you may send us a return email asking to be omitted from future email distributions.
* **Targeted Advertising**.  If you do not want us to use information that we collect or that you provide to us to deliver advertisements according to our advertisers’ target-audience preferences, you can opt-out by sending us an email stating your request to [\[email protected\]](https://www.themirror.space/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).  

We do not control third-parties’ collection or use of your information to serve interest-based advertising.  However, these third-parties may provide you with ways to choose not to have your information collected or used in this way.  You can opt-out of receiving targeted ads from users of the Network Advertising Initiative (“**NAI**”) on the NAI’s website: ([https://www.thenai.org/](https://www.thenai.org/)).

You can review and change your personal information by logging into the Service and visiting your account profile page.

**Your California Privacy Rights**

If you are a California resident, California law may provide you with additional rights regarding our use of your personal information.  To learn more about your California privacy rights, visit [https://oag.ca.gov/privacy/ccpa](https://oag.ca.gov/privacy/ccpa).

California’s “shine the Light” law (Civil Code Section § 1798.83) permits users of our App that are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third-parties for their direct marketing purposes.  To make such a request, please send an email to [\[email protected\]](https://www.themirror.space/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) or write us at: 7901 4th St N, Suite 15196, St. Petersburg FL 33702.

**Your Nevada Privacy Rights**

If you are a resident of Nevada, you have the right to opt-out of the sale of certain personal information to third parties who intend to license or sell that personal information.  You can exercise this right by contacting us as set forth in “Contact Us” below with the subject line “Nevada Do Not Sell Request” and providing us with your name and the email address associated with your account. Please note that we do not currently sell your personal information as sales are defined in Nevada Revised Statutes Chapter 603A.

**International Users**

If you are located outside of the United States, please note that the Service is located on computer servers in the United States.  Therefore, your information may be processed and stored in the United States.  As a result, United States federal and state governments, courts, or law enforcement or regulatory agencies may be able to obtain disclosure of your information through laws applicable in the United States.  Your use of the Service or your submission of any Personal Information to us will constitute your consent to the transfer of your Personal Information outside of your home country, (including the United States), which may provide for different data protection rules than in your country.  Please also _see_ the Supplemental Privacy Policy section for European Economic Area residents.

**Data Security**

We have implemented measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration, and disclosure.

The safety and security of your information also depends on you.  Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password for access to certain parts of our Service, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential.  We ask you not to share your password with anyone.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure.  Although we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted to our Service.  Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk.  We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained in our Platform.

**Changes to Our Privacy Policy**

It is our policy to post any changes we make to our Privacy Policy on this page, with a notice that the privacy policy has been updated on the Website home page.  The date the privacy policy was last revised is identified at the top of the page.  You are responsible for periodically visiting our Website and this Privacy Policy to check for any changes.

**Contact Information**

To ask questions and/or comment about this Privacy Policy and our Privacy Practices, contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.themirror.space/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

‍
